SEIU Local 200 Syracuse University Library Strike Files 5949
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
SEIU Local 200 Syracuse University Library Strike Files
1967-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
SEIU Local 200
5949
1.11 cubic feet
1.1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5736601
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 21, 2005
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4191 AV: ILR School Audio-Visual Department Video Cassette Collection 6174/001: NYSUT President's Office Files 6287: Martin Scheinman Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements 6347 PUBS: 1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Publications
Service industries workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Labor unions -- Law and legislation -- New York (State); Service Employees International Union; Service Employees International Union. Local 200.; Syracuse University 650: Labor unions--Law and legislation--New York (State)
5736601
- Agreements & contracts 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Articles. Photocopies, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Clippings. 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Clippings 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Clippings. "Daily Orange" 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Constitution & ByLaws 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Job Descriptions (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Hillman, Diane. Personal, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Local 200, News Bulletin. 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Memos, Correspondence & Grievances 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Newsletter, Bulletin & Reports 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Notes, Statistics, Meeting Minutes, Questionnaires, Misc. 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Petitions. 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Posters & Flyers. No Data. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Press Releases, Open Letters, Public Memorandums. 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Staff Guides & Manuals 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Syracuse University. Annual Report. 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Syracuse Univ. Library clerks strike poster (Box 2)